hdfcsec.com 2008-12-17

# HDFC Securities

|    |  |  About Us  |  Careers  |  FAQs  |  Site Map  |  Branch Locator  |  Feedback  
---  
   
Tools  |  Register Here  
| Investor| | Trader| | NRI |  |    |  New to this site ? Click Here |  Set as Homepage  
---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---  
Equity   |   Derivatives   |   Mutual Funds   |   IPO| Tools   |   News   |   Research   |   Knowledge Center   |   Charting   |   Customer Care  
  
You are here : Home > About Us > Privacy

|  About Us  
---  
Profile  
Our Offerings  
Privacy  
Disclaimer  
Did You Know ?  
---  
Your Age And Your In...  
Age plays a key role in determining your investment profile. Hence, constru...  
 More  
  
| 

| Statement on privacy and security

At HDFC Securities we are strongly committed to protecting the personal and financial information that you submit to us. This information is provided when you register to receive certain HDFC Securities services or products, such as online share trading. The personal information we get from you will help us provide you with improved services and products that match your needs as closely as possible.   
  
---  
We shall not sell your personal information to any third party. However under certain conditions we would share this information :  
We share information as part of normal business operations, such as providing you with any services to which you subscribe, and any activity related to these services such as collecting fees for those services, and informing you about these services;  
as part of normal legal/regulatory purposes required by the Securities and Exchange Board of India and other regulatory and government entities, and   
We may occasionally invite selected third parties to participate in offers we feel would be attractive to customers of HDFC Securities customers.  
  
It may become necessary for HDFC Securities to disclose your personal information to our agents and contractors, or to their subcontractors. However these parties would be required to use the information obtained from HDFC Securities for such use exclusively. 

Your account information is protected by placing it in the secure portion of our Web site, which is why you need to enter your unique login username and password each time you want to access your account information. 

Do help us protect your privacy by maintaining the secrecy of the username and password you use for any of our services. 

Please note that this privacy policy does not create any contractual or other legal rights in or on behalf of any party, nor is it intended to do so.   
  
|  |   
---|---  

|  [BSE](http://www.bseindia.com/)  |  [NSE](http://www.nseindia.com/)  |  [SEBI](http://www.sebi.gov.in/)  |  [HDFC](http://www.hdfc.com/)  |  [ HDFC Bank](http://www.hdfcbank.com/)  |  [HDFC MF](http://www.hdfcfund.com/)  |  [HDFCRealty](http://www.hdfcrealty.com/)  |  [HDFCStdLife](http://www.hdfcinsurance.com/)  |  [HDFC ERGO](http://www.hdfcergo.com/)  | BSE Disclaimer |   Privacy Policy  |   Disclaimer  
---|---  
|  Copyright © 2007. All rights Reserved. HDFC Securities Limited.  
Designed & Developed by [Idealake Information Technologies Pvt. Ltd.](http://www.idealake.com/)  
Content provided by [Capital Market](http://www.capitalmarket.com/).  
Site best viewed in IE 5.0+, Netscape 8.1 and Mozila Firefox 1.5+ at 800 x 600 pixels resolution.  
All rights reserved. NSE: CM: INB 231109431 FO: INF 231109431 CURRENCY DERIVATIVES: TM & CM - INE 231109431 BSE: CM: INB 011109437 FO: INF 011109437 PMS: INP000000928 AMFI ARN NO. 13549 IRDA - CORPORATE AGENT .LICENCE NO. 2806925 COMPANY REGISTRATION NO. U67120MH2000PLC152193  HDFC Securities Limited | AMFI ARN No.13549
